Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, light bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Bursar (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago Comptroller (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, bills paid (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes Observatory petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes Observatory payroll (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago fellowship applications University of Chicago Divisional Office University of Chicago Gale (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Hutchins University of Chicago Library (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Milky Way, 1937 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago University of Chicago bulletins and notices (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1937 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Photo Department, 1937 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Publicity University of Chicago Purchasing Agent (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago requisitions (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - U, 1937, University of Chicago, students, summer 1937 University of Chicago, classes, colloquia, students work (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago, reports, 1937 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander (University of Chicago Press), 1938 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Astrophysical Journal, reprints, 1938 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - A, 1938, Astrophysical Journal, bills Astrophysical Journal, Seares Astrophysical Journal, finances (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - A, 1938, Astrophysical Journal Astrophysical Journal, subscription reports (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - A, 1938, Abetti, Giorgio, 2 pages A. Adams and Company, 1 page Adams, C. H., 4 pages Adams, W. S., 10 pages Adel, Arthur, 7 pages Addressograph Sales Agency, 2 pages Adrian, Professor, 2 pages Aitken, Robert G., 6 pages Albrecht, Sebastian, 1 page Allen, Leah B., 4 pages Aller, Lawrence H., 1 page Allison, Samuel K., 8 pages Alton Railroad Company, 1 page Aluminum Company America, 2 pages American Air Lines, 1 page American Amateur Astronomical Association, 1 page American Association Advancement Science, 8 pages American Association University Women, 1 page American Astronomical Society, 11 pages American Documentation Institute, 7 pages American Ephemeris and Nautical Almanac, 1 page American Mathematical Society, 1 page American Nautical Academy, 3 pages American Philosophical Society, 9 pages American Physics Teacher, 1 page Amstutz, N. S., 3 pages Anderson, J. A., 9 pages Andrews, Roy C. (American Museum), 1 page Arctureans, 1 page Associated Press, 1 page Astronomical Journal, 2 pages Astronomisches Rechen-Institute, 1 page Austin Hotel, 2 pages (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - A-B, 1938, Applications for positions, 1 page Baade, Walter, 1 page Babcock, Harold D., 3 pages Baker, Robert H., 2 pages Baker, Stewart R., 5 pages Baldwin, Ralph B., 10 pages Barbarian, A., 2 pages Barrett, Ida C., 1 page Barth, Johannes A., 1 page Bartky, Walter, 9 pages Bausch and Lomb, 5 pages Beals, C. S., 10 pages Becker, Friedrich, 2 pages Behncke, Nile, 2 pages Belgian Consul, 1 page Benedict, Ada, 1 page Bennett, Arthur L., 3 pages Bennott, Mand, 1 page Benton, Junior, 2 pages Bernheimer, W., 1 page Biermann, L., 2 page Bjorge, Carl, 1 page Blair, G. B., 2 pages Blair, Julian M., 1 page Blakslee, G., 2 pages Bliss, P. E., 4 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 33 pages Bok, B. J., 37 pages Bond, Fred C., 2 pages Boss, Benjamin, 9 pages Breit, Gregory, 16 pages British Astronomical Association, 1 page ten Bruggencate, P., 1 page Brown University, 1 page van Brunn, A., 2 pages Bureau des longitudes, 1 page Burns, Keivin, 8 pages Burrell, Mrs. Edward, 10 pages (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - B-C, 1938, Bowens Image Slicer Calvert, Mary R., 1 page Campbell, Mrs. W. W., 2 pages Carpenter, Edwin F., 5 pages Casey, S. K., 3 pages Cattell, J. McKeen, 6 pages Chance Brothers, 4 pages Chandrasekhar, S., 2 pages Chattanooga Observatory, 1 page Cherrington, Ernest, Jr., 1 page Chicago Astronomical Society, 12 pages Chicago Motor Club, 3 pages China National Central Library, 1 page Clausing, Leroy M. E., 15 pages Hotel Cleveland, 4 pages Coe, Jerome T., 2 pages Cohn, Willi M., 1 page Collier and Son, 3 pages Collins, O. C., 7 pages Corning Glass Works, 1 page Customs Collector, 1 page Cunard White Star, 2 pages (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - D-E, 1938, Daniel, Z., 1 page Davis, Dorothy, 15 pages Dejardin, G., 5 pages Demees, J. B., 1 page Devany, Arthur, 5 pages Devoe and Raynolds Company, 1 page Doty, R. E., 5 pages Douglas, A. E., 2 pages Dow Chemical Company, 2 pages Downing, Elliot R., 1 page Dowsett, H. M., 2 pages Dufay, J., 5 pages Dugan, R. S., 9 pages Duncan, John C., 10 pages Durham, Theodore, 4 pages E. P. Dutton and Company, 1 page Eastman Kodak Company, 16 pages Ebbighausen, E. G., 1 page Ebell, M., 2 pages Emerson, Alfred E., 2 pages Encyclopaedia Britannica, 3 pages Engle, Paul R., 2 pages Esser, Martin, 2 pages Evaporated Meal Films Corporation, 8 pages (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - F, 1938, Fairbanks-Morse Company, 2 pages Farnsworth, Alice H., 4 pages Fecker, J. W., 4 pages Fish Schurman Corporation, 12 pages Flammarion, Gabrielle, 1 page Fock, Gustav, 1 page Fox, Philip, 12 pages France, Certificate from Exposition 1937, 1 page Franck, James, 1 page Franklin Institute, 1 page Freundlich, E. F., 9 pages First National Bank (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - G, 1938, G. M. Laboratories, 5 pages Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 7 pages Gamow, G., 4 pages Gaposchkin, Cecilia Payne, 1 page Gaposchkin, Sergei, 10 pages Garrett, W. H., 1 page Gaudet, G., 3 pages General Electric Supply Corporation, 10 pages Geneva Lake Home Owners Protective Association, 6 pages Ghosh, M. K., 2 pages Gingrich, C. H., 36 pages Girling, Sidney S., 8 pages Goldberg, Leo, 13 pages Graflex, 3 pages Grams, F. O., 1 page Greaves, W. M. H., 1 page Green, Henry J., 1 page Greenstein, Jesse L., 27 pages Grotian, W., 3 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 5 pages Gussow, M., 2 pages Guthnick, P., 1 page (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - H, 1938, Haas, Arthur, 2 pages Hacker, Sidney G., 4 pages Haffner, H., 11 pages Hagemann, F. G., 2 pages Hagihara, Y., 3 pages Hall, G. E., 1 page Hall, John S., 2 pages Harper, W. E., 4 pages Harrison, George R., 2 pages Harshaw Chemical Company, 5 pages Harvard College Observatory, 2 pages Hassler, J. O., 1 page Heard, J., 1 page Hedengren, T. R., 2 pages Hemml, G., 1 page Henyey, L., 12 pages Hertzsprung, Ejnar, 20 pages Herzberg, G., 2 pages Hesselberg, T. L., 2 pages Hesthal, C. E., 3 pages Hetzler, 2 pages Hogness, T. R., 1 page Holcomb, G. E., 3 pages Holland Hall, 1 page Holloway, W. R., 2 pages Home Lumber and Fuel Company, 1 page Hope-Jones, F., 4 pages Houghton Mifflin, 1 page Howe, John P. (Office of the President), 11 pages Hubble, E. P., 2 pages Huffer, C. M., 7 pages Hujer, Karel, 1 page Hunter, A., 2 pages Hynek, J. A., 35 pages (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - International Astronomical Union, 1938 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - J-K, 1938, Jahn and Ollier, 2 pages James, Hubert M., 7 pages Jefferson, Edward N., 2 pages Jones and Laughlin, 1 page Jordan, Frank C., 2 pages Kaempffert, W. (New York Times), 3 pages Kaiser, Thomas K., 1 page Karmel, Gottfried, 2 pages Kearney and Trecker, 4 pages Keenan, P. C., 7 pages Keller, Ernest G., 1 page Kerkhof, N., 2 pages Keystone View Company, 2 pages Kiel Institute fur Theoretische Physik, 1 page Kienle, H., 1 page Kinnaird, Richard, 1 page Kneale, Elmer J., 1 page Kobold, H., 5 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 4 pages Koehler and Amelang, 2 pages Kogler, Rudolf, 5 pages Kohler Company (H. J. Thorkelson), 1 page Kopff, A., 2 pages Kothari, D. S., 6 pages Kreiken, E. A., 2 pages Krieger, C. J., 17 pages Kuiper, G. P., 9 pages (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - L, 1938, Ladenburg, R., 1 page Lawton, Harry, 2 pages Lee, Oliver J., 6 pages Leeds and Northrup Company, 2 pages Lemon, Harvey B., 9 pages Leuschner, A. O., 1 page Lindblad, N., 2 pages Lindsay, E. M., 2 pages Linke, Walter R., 7 pages Losch, Hazel M., 2 pages Lower, Harold A., 8 pages Luby, Wm. A., 2 pages Luyten, W. J., 3 pages Luyten Paper, 47 pages (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - M, 1938, McCarthy, Edward L., 16 pages McCusky, S. W., 3 pages McLaughlin, Dean B., 11 pages McLeod, Noah W., 2 pages McManus, L. A. (F. W. Faxon), 2 pages McMath, Robert R., 9 pages MacMillan Company, 2 pages Marchant Calculating, 6 pages Markowitz, William, 1 page Martz, E. P., Jr., 7 pages Mead, E. K., 2 pages Menzel, Donald H., 29 pages Merrill, Paul W., 4 pages Micro Switch Corporation, 3 pages Miedel, Edward, 2pages Milham, Williams, 1 page Miller, F. D., 9 pages Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 5 pages Milwaukee Public Museum, 1 page Mineur, Henri, 8 pages Minnaert, M., 2 pages Mitchell, S. A., 2 pages Mitteilung Astronomische Nachrichten, 1 page Moffitt, G. W., 1 page Mohlet, Orren, 2 pages Mohler, Orren, 2 pages Monk, George S., 3 pages Monningh, D., 2 pages Moore, J. H., 4 pages Morelock, H. W., 2 pages Mosher, F. J., 2 pages Mowbray, Albert G., 3 pages Mulders, F. G. W., 1 page Mulliken, R. S., 17 pages (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - N, 1938, Nassau, J. J., 15 pages National Academy of Sciences, 42 pages National Research Council, 9 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 2 pages Nedilow, A. A., 4 pages New York Academy of Sciences, 1 page Newschronicle (London), 1 page Neyman, J., 1 page Nielsen, J. Rud, 4 pages Northfield News, 1 page Norton, W. J., 2 pages Notre Dame Symposium, 2 pages Nyland, G. F., 2 pages (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - O, 1938, O’Brien, Brian, 16 pages O’Conner, C., 2 pages O’Keefe, John A., 3 pages O’Leary, Raymond, 1 page Oort, J. H., 1 page Oppenheimer, Harry D., 3 pages Otis Elevator, 1 page Oxford University Press, 2 pages Orders for publications (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - P, 1938, Page, Thornton, 6 pages Parsons, P. W., 2 pages Pearce, J. A., 2 pages Pearson, Fred, 10 pages Pekeris, C., 9 pages Pendray, G. Edward, 5 pages Petrie, R. M., 9 pages Pettit, Edison, 2 pages Plakides, S., 2 pages Plaskett, J. S., 14 pages Pogo, Alexander, 1 page Preston, L. R. (Commonwealth Edison), 6 pages Page appointment Paradox (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Questions, 1938 (Box 174, Folder 8-9)
  - R, 1938, Railway Express Company, 5 pages Ramensky, Peter, 2 pages Rashevsky, N., 3 pages Rayleigh, Lord, 2 pages Reinhold Publishing Corporation, 1 page Rieke, Carol A., 6 pages Rimmer, W. B., 2 pages Roach, F. E., 14 pages University of Rochester News Bureau, 2 pages Rockefeller Foundation, 3 pages Rogers, F. T. Jr., 10 pages Rood, Paul, 1 page Ross, F. E., 11 pages Rosseland, S., 1 page Rotary Club, 2 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 3 pages Royal Society of Arts, 1 page Royal Typewriter Company, 1 page Rudnick, Paul and Jessie, 15 pages Russell, Henry Norris, 37 pages (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - S, 1938, Shapley, 34 pages Struve, 59 pages (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Symposium, Physics Astronomy, 1938 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - S, 1938, Sayer, Arthur R., 4 pages Schilt, Jan, 2 pages Schlesinger, Frank, 12 pages Schoenberg, E., 3 pages Schwede, Harold and Christine Westgate, 2 pages Science Service, 2 pages Scientia, 1 page Seiders, F. W., 1 page Senior, James K., 4 pages Seyfert, C. K., 10 pages Sherman, F., 5 pages Sigma Xi, 14 pages The Sky, 3 pages Slocum, Lois T., 2 pages Smiley, Charles H., 5 pages Somerville, D. S., 2 pages Soper, Edmund D., 3 pages Sproul Observatory, 2 pages Standard Oil Company, 1 page Stebbins, Joel, 4 pages G. E. Stechert and Company, 3 pages Steel Sales Corporation, 1 page Stephens, Jessica Y., 3 pages Sterges, Alfred, 2 pages Sterne, T. E., 22 pages (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - S, 1938, Stetson, Harlan T., 5 pages Stewart, John W., 6 pages Sticker, B., 3 pages Stocks, John, 3 pages Stratton, F. J. M., 11 pages Stromberg, G., 1 page Stromgren, Bengt, 22 pages Stromgren, Elias, 3 pages Struve family, 3 pages Swings, P., 43 pages (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - S, 1938, Slitless spectrograph Schmidt camera (20") (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - T-V, 1938, Takanime, T., 6 pages Taylor, C. W. (P. F. Collier and Son), 3 pages Teller, Edward, 1 page Ten Bruggencate, P., 3 pages Teubner, B. G., 1 page Texas Observers, 6 pages Thomas, L. H., 4 pages Thorkelson, H. J. (Kohler Company), 2 pages Titus, John, 7 pages Tohoku Imperial University, 1 page Tracht, Fred (University of Chicago Bookstore), 2 pages Truman, O. H., 9 pages Unsold, A., 10 pages United Airlines, 12 pages United States Post Office, 6 pages United States Treasury (Customs), 3 pages Uzefovich, A. M., 3 pages Vallarta, M. S., 1 page Van Biesbroeck, G., 3 pages Van de Kamp, P., 6 pages Vegard, L., 3 pages Venable, William M., 2 pages Volunteer Fire Department Williams Bay, 1 page Von Struve, A. W., 3 pages (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Visitors, 1938 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - W-Z, 1938, Wagman, N. E., 1 page Walker, Arville D., 1 page Walters, Francis M. Jr., 2 pages Wares, Gordon, 4 pages Warner and Swasey Company, 5 pages Warsaw Institute D’Astronomie Pratique, 2 pages Watts, Maxine, 3 pages Wells, H. B., 4 pages West, Alvin M., 3 pages Western Reserve Academy, 4 pages Whitney, Walter T., 2 pages Wildt, Rupert, 12 pages George Williams College, 4 pages Williams, Robley C., 8 pages Wilson, Edwin B., 3 pages Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, 2 pages Wisconsin Power and Light, 3 pages Woodbury, David O., 1 page Woolley, R. V. D. R., 2 pages Wright, W. H., 2 pages Wurm, K., 19 pages Yale University Library, 2 pages Yanitz, Murray (Fish-Schurman), 2 pages YMCA, 3 pages Yu, C. S., 2 pages Carl Zeiss, 2 pages Zimmerman, Walter W., 4 pages Zonn, W., 2 pages Zwicky, F., 6 pages (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1938 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, accident reports University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, light bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Bursar (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago Comptroller (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Comptroller McDonald, payroll, petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller Yerkes, payroll, petty cash (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Division, Gale, 1938 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Divisional Office, department change, 1938 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Division, courses University of Chicago Division, fellowship applications (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Hutchins University of Chicago Filbey (Vice President) University of Chicago Library (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Milky Way University of Chicago University of Chicago bulletins, notices (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Press University of Chicago Photo Department (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Publicity, 1938 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago Purchasing Department University of Chicago Registrar (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - U, 1938, University of Chicago reports University of Chicago colloquia (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago requisitions, 1938 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander, 1939 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - A, 1939, Astrophysical Journal, bills Astrophysical Journal, missing numbers (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - A, 1939, Astrophysical Journal, finances Astrophysical Journal, reprint orders (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - A, 1939, Astrophysical Journal, Seares Astrophysical Journal, subscription reports Astrophysical Journal (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - A, 1939, Abbott, C. E., 2 pages Abetti, G., 1 page Adams, W. S., 8 pages Adel, Arthur, 16 pages Agfa Ansco, 6 pages Aitken, Robert G., 15 pages Alter, Dinsmore, 5 pages Alumni Council, 7 pages Amarillo College, 1 page American Airlines, 11 pages American Association to Advance Science, 1 page American Astrological Society, 7 pages American College Bureau, 4 pages American Documentation Institute, 1 page American Institute of Physics, 1 page American Mathematical Society, 3 pages American Philosophical Society, 21 pages American Scandinavian Foundation, 1 page Anderson, C. D., 2 pages Anderson, C. N. (Bell Labs), 3 pages Annear, Paul, 1 page Arakawa, H., 3 pages Society of Architecture, History and Art, 3 pages Arrowood, Charles F., 5 pages Asociation Argentina Amigos de la Astronomia, 1 page Assessor of Incomes, Racine, 4 pages Associated Press, 1 page Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 9 pages Atkins, John E., 1 page N. W. Ayer and Son, 5 pages (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - A, 1939, American Association for the Advancement of Science meeting Milwaukee Applications for positions (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - B, 1939, Baade, W., 1 page Babcock, H. W., 9 pages Bachrach Studios, 2 pages Bailey, Edwin M., Jr., 7 pages Baird Associates, 2 pages Baldwin, Ralph B., 27 pages Baldwin-Wallace College, 1 page Barbier, D., 7 pages Barragan, Manuel M., 2 pages Barrett, S. A., 2 pages Bartky, Walter, 8 pages Bausch and Lomb, 11 pages Beals, C. S., 7 pages Beer, Arthur, 5 pages Beljawsky, F., 2 pages Bennett, Arthur L., 1 page Bentsen, H. B., 2 pages Bernhard, Rene, 1 page Bertraud, Charles, 3 pages Beutler, Hans, 5 pages Bliss, Philip E., 1 page Blitzer, Leon, 6 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 9 pages Bok, B., 16 pages Bonsdorff, I., 1 page Boss, Benjamin, 2 pages Boston International Salon of Nature Photography, 1 page Boyer, Jacques, 4 pages Bradley, J. E., 2 pages Brazil, Director de Propaganda, 1 page Breit, G., 24 pages Briggs, Lyman J., 2 pages Brilhart, F. B., 2 pages British Astronomical Association, 2 pages Brown University, 1 page Buhl Foundation, 4 pages Buttrick, J. F., 2 pages Bowens Image Slicer (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - C, 1939, Calder, W. G., 4 pages Calhoun, J. W. (Texas University), 4 pages Calvert, Mary M., 2 pages Carnaps, R., 2 pages Carnera, P., 2 pages Carpenter, Edwin F., 1 page Case School of Applied Science, 1 page Cattell, J. McKeen, 3 pages Central Scientific Company, 2 pages Chalonge, D., 3 pages Champion Recording Company, 1 page Chandrasekhar, S., 12 pages Chant, C. A., 1 page Chapman, S., 5 pages Cherrington, Ernest, 4 pages Chicago Astronomical Society, 7 pages C. R. Childs Company, 2 pages Clausing, Leroy M. E., 1 page P. F. Collier and Son, 1 page Compton, Arthur J., 11 pages Conklin, E. G., 4 pages Corning Glass Works, 2 pages John Crerar Library, 2 pages F. S. Crofts and Company, 3 pages Colloquia Coronaviser (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - D, 1939, Davis, Dorothy N., 9 pages Davis, Watson (Science Service), 20 pages Dejardin, G., 5 pages DeMees, J. B., 2 pages Deutsch, Armin, 3 pages DeVany, Arthur (Schmidt camera), 57 pages Dimitroff, George Z., 1 page Dodd, Mead and Company, 2 pages Dodson, Helen, 2 pages Dominion Observatory, New Zealand, 1 page Duesberg, J., 3 pages Dufay, J., 6 pages Dugan, Raymond S., 2 pages Duncan, John C., 4 pages Dunham, Theodore, 18 pages E. I. DuPont De Nemours, 1 page (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - E-F, 1939, Eastman Kodak Company, 27 pages Eaton, Cyrus, 2 pages Ebbighausen, Edwin, 32 pages Elvey, 3 pages Employment office, 1 page Fairbank, Mrs. Kellogg, 3 pages Farnsworth, Alice H., 3 pages Fecker, J. W., 2 pages Feynman, R. P., 2 pages Finnell System, 2 pages Fish-Schurman Corporation, 6 pages Fisher, Clyde, 3 pages Flammarion, Gabrielle, 6 pages Fox, Philip, 2 pages Franck, James, 6 pages Freundlich, E. F., 1 page Friend, Clarence L., 2 pages Frost Biography, 3 pages (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - F-G, 1939, First National Bank Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 4 pages Gamow, G., 4 pages Gaposchkin, Cecilia Payne, 6 pages Gaposchkin, Sergei, 2 pages Garrett, W. H., 1 page Geiger, Edward J., 2 pages Geneva Lake Home Owners Association, 4 pages Gingrich, C. H., 14 pages GM Laboratories, 6 pages Godart, 2 pages Goedicke, Victors A., 13 pages Goldberg, Leo, 10 pages Golub, N., 2 pages Goodspeed, C. T. B., 2 pages Green, Warren K., 2 pages Greenstein, Jesse, 23 pages Grotrian, W., 1 page Guggenheim Foundation, 7 pages Guthnick, F., 2 pages (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - H, 1939, Haimo, Franklin, 6 pages Hall, John S., 14 pages Hardy, Arthur C., 2 pages Harvard College Observatory, 9 pages Vase and Koehler, 2 pages Havens, Paul S., 2 pages Heinmiller, Helen (Warner and Swasey), 2 pages Hemmindinger, Henry, 3 pages Henrich, Louis R., 6 pages Hertzsprung, Ejnar, 1 page Herzberg, G., 2 pages Hesthal, C. E., 1 page Hetzler, Charles, 16 pages Hofferberth, G. F., 2 pages Hoffleit, Dorrit, 3 pages Johns Hopkins University, 2 pages Hopmann, J., 3 pages Huffer, R. C., 4 pages Hutchisson, Elmer, 4 pages Hynek, J. A., 22 pages (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - I-J 1939, Immigrant Americans (Louis Adamic), 2 pages Ingalls, Albert G., 3 pages Inglis, D. R., 5 pages International Astronomical Union, 46 pages Jamison, N. C. (Sigma Xi), 2 pages Jehle, Herbert, 3 pages (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Jahn and Ollier, 1939 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - K, 1939, Kane, Ellis D., 1 page Keenan, P. C., 12 pages Keller, Ernest G., 1 page Kinnaird, R. F., 4 pages Kneale, Elmer J., 8 pages Knox-Shaw, H., 2 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 2 pages Konig, Arthur, 5 pages Kopal, Z., 2 pages Kopff, A., 1 page Krieger, C. J., 29 pages Kruger, Friedrich, 1 page Kuehne, J. M., 1 page Kuiper, G. P., 51 pages (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - L, 1939, LaVanture, Mrs. L. A., 2 pages Lawford, Roscoe, 1 page Lee, Cuthbert, 2 pages Lee, Oliver J., 8 pages Lemon, Harvey B., 3 pages Leningrad Astronomical Institute, 1 page Levine, Joseph, 1 page Lick Observatory, plane crash, 2 pages Lindblad, Bertil, 7 pages Link, George K. K., 2 pages Linsley, Earle G., 5 pages Lleras, J. A., 3 pages Los Angeles City College, 2 pages Lower, Harold A., 7 pages Luby, William A., 2 pages Luft, Herbert, 2 pages Lundin, C. A. R., 1 page Luyten, W. J., 43 pages (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - M, 1939, Macmillan and Company, 2 pages Makemso, Maud W., 5 pages Mantler, J. Robert, 2 pages Marchant, 1 page Marko, Ronald J., 1 page Marshak, R. E., 11 pages Marshall, Roy K., 2 pages Marshall, Thomas, 8 pages Martz, Edwin P., 40 pages International Congress of Mathematicians, 1 page Mayall, Mrs. R. Newton, 2 pages Mellish, John E., 16 pages Menzel, Donald, 23 pages Merrill, Paul W., 9 pages Milham, Willis I., 3 pages Milne, E. A., 3 pages Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 5 pages Mirovedenie (translation), 7 pages Mitchell, S. A., 5 pages Miyamoto, Shotaro, 1 page Moffitt, G. W., 10 pages Mohler, F. L., 1 page Monk, George S., 9 pages Moore, G. C., 10 pages Moore, J. H., 4 pages Morehouse, D. W., 2 pages Morris, Donald, 3 pages Mort, Howard W., 1 page Moulton, F. R., 3 pages Mullikin, R. S., 21 pages (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - M, 1939, McCarthy, E. L., 3 pages McCusky, S. W., 3 pages McGill, William L., 1 page McLaughlin, Dean B., 10 pages McLeod, Noah, 1 page Monograph (Box 180, Folder 6)